liveinstyle.com 2018-01-22

# Privacy & Cookie Policy | LiveInStyle

This **Privacy and Cookie Notice** provides a high-level overview of our full **Privacy and Cookie Notice** (see section 1 for more information).  It summarises important information regarding how we collect, use, and share any personal information collected. This Privacy and Cookie Notice applies to personal information collected through this website, which is operated by United Spirits Limited a Diageo Group Company.

**1\. Introduction**

  * See section 1 for more information about **United Spirits Limited** and its parent entity **Diageo** **plc**

****2**** ** **. Are you of legal purchase age?**                                     **

  * Do not provide us with your personal information if you are not of legal age to purchase alcohol.
  * If we believe that you are under the legal purchase age we will make every reasonable effort to remove your personal information from our records. 

**3\. What is personal information?**                     

  * Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, as defined by applicable law.    

**4.  USL’s collection and use of personal information** 

  * We collect personal information that you choose to provide. This includes information provided when registering with the website, contacting us, completing surveys or questionnaires, entering competitions, promotional features, sweepstakes and posting information on public areas of our websites.
  * When you use this and other Diageo websites (including by browsing such sites) some information about your visit is automatically recorded such as the pages you have viewed, your IP address and the date and time of your visit.  We also collect information using cookies.
  * By using this website, you are agreeing to our use of that information as set out in this Privacy and Cookie Notice.

  * **If you do not agree to these conditions, please do not provide us with this information, or please let us know your objections using the contact details below.**

****5\. Use of cookies on our websites****

We use "cookies" to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website, cookies help us gather and store information about visitors. To find out more information about how we use cookies, please refer to section 6.

If you continue without changing your settings, we’ll assume that you accept the use of cookies in accordance with this Privacy & Cookies Notice. If you do not accept the use of cookies, please refer to section 12 and 13 to find out how to disable cookies.

We also collect information using common Internet technologies such as “cookies” and “ **clear** **gifs** ” (also known as “ **web** **bugs** ” or “ **web** **beacons** ”).

  * See section 6 for more information.

**6\. Use of IP addresses**

When your web browser or e-mail application requests a web page or e-mail from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This is called your computer's "IP address." (IP stands for "Internet protocol.") For most users accessing the Internet from a dial-up Internet service provider (I6P), the IP address will be different every time you log on. We do not store IP addresses in a central database.  They are just recorded in log files so they are not associated with an account.

 IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including to:

  * to  identify a person’s country access.
  * To assist our third party service provider to manage GEO IP location, who may map IP addresses to countries.
  * Diagnose service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
  * Send the most appropriate advertising based on geographic area or information derived from your IP address. Many IP addresses are commonly associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major corporations in specific regions or localities. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.
  * Estimate the total number of users visiting our websites from specific countries or regions of the world.
  * Assist third party advertisers to track effectiveness of the promotions they run on our website, visits to and business at third party's websites.
  * Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content that we host.

**7\. Use of personal Information**

  * We will only use the personal information we collect: for our legitimate business interests, including to improve your consumer experience of our products and services, the Site, to provide you with specific information and services that you request, such additional information and services that may be of interest to you, studying user behaviour and for other business purpose of USL.

**8\. Disclosure of personal Information**

  * This may involve sharing your personal information with non-Diageo companies that provide services to Diageo companies and certain other third parties, but only where they have adequate protection to safeguard and hold your personal information securely or where you have provided your consent.
  * In some cases, this may involve transferring your personal information to other countries (including the U.K., the U.S., Canada and countries in the European Economic Area) where Diageo or non-Diageo companies or other third parties operate and process your personal information.   To the extent that we do share your personal information with a service provider, we would only do so if we have entered into a written agreement with that party and that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this privacy policy.
  * **By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and clearly consent to such use and transfers as set out in this Privacy and Cookie Notice and our full Privacy and Cookie Notice.**

****9\. Public areas of our website****

  * Information that you post on or through the public areas of the site (e.g. chat rooms, bulletin boards and discussion groups) are generally accessible to, and may be collected and used by, others.

**10\. Security**

  * We take security seriously and take precautions to keep your personal information secure We have implemented security practices and procedures and have a comprehensively documented information security programme and information security policies with adequate managerial, technical, operational and physical security control measures to safeguard against any non-disclosure of your personal information that we collect.
  * Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us at the contact details below.

We have no control over the privacy of any communications while in transit to us. We recommend that you not include confidential, proprietary or sensitive information in such communications. See section 16 for more information

**11\. Unsubscribe, access, questions and further information       **

  * At your request, and where required by law, we will confirm, share, and/or update the personal information we hold about you.  However, to protect your privacy we may first have to verify your identity, including by using your registered user name and accessing your user account.
  * At any time you can choose to make an **unsubscribe request** to stop receiving direct marketingcommunications.
  * If you would like to unsubscribe from communications from Diageo or about Diageo brands, please contact: **admin@liveinstyle.com]**
  * See section 17 for more information on your choices.

**12\. Retention period**

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.  

**13.  Contact Us**

If you have any comments, queries, or complaints about our collection or use of personal information please contact us via:

  * **Post:** Level 8, UB Tower, UB City, 24 Vittal Mallya Road, Bangalore –
  * **Email: admin@liveinstyle.com**
  * **Telephone: 080-39856908**

### PRIVACY AND COOKIE NOTICE

### **1.  Introduction**

This website is operated by United Spirits Limited, a member of the Diageo group of companies, having its registered office at Level 6-10, UB Tower, UB City, 24 Vittal Mallya Road, Bangalore – 560001 (“USL”), the ultimate holding company of which is Diageo plc (registered in England and Wales with company number 23307 and registered address at Lakeside Drive, London, NW10 7HQ, United Kingdom).

All references to 'our', 'us', 'we', or ‘company’ within this policy and within the opt-in notice are deemed to refer to USL, Diageo plc, its subsidiaries, affiliates, and/or associates, as appropriate.

We endeavour to protect your personal privacy. We provide this Privacy and Cookie Notice to help you to understand what we may do with any personal information that we obtain from you. By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy and Cookie Notice and agree that we may collect, use, and disclose your personal information as described in this Privacy and Cookie Notice. If you do not agree to this Notice, please do not use the site. This Privacy and Cookie Notice is incorporated into, and part of, the Conditions of Use, that govern your use of the site in general. We will use your information only for the purposes set forth below.

We may need to update this Privacy and Cookie Notice from time to time. We recommend that you check this page regularly to ensure that you have read the most recent version.

Changes to the Privacy and Cookie Notice are noted here:

Date last revised: 30.06.2016

Description of substantive revisions:

_Section 3 – Description of personal information_

_Section 4 – Description of how personal information is collected_

_Section 5 – Use of IP Address_

_Section 6 – Use of cookies and clear gifs_

_Section 14 – Description of how personal information is used_

_Section 15 – Description of how personal information is shared_

_Section 16 – Posting of information in public forums_

_Section 20 – Changes to your privacy preferences_

Section 21 – Description of use of links, references, interfaces, and content from  
third-party sites

### **2.  Legal purchase age**

You must not provide us with your personal information if you are not of legal age to purchase alcohol in the jurisdiction in which you reside and (if different) in the jurisdiction in which you are accessing the site. We do not intend to collect personal information from any individuals under the legal purchase age, or to market alcoholic beverages to anyone under the legal purchase age. If we receive notice or believe that someone under the legal purchase age has provided us with personal information we will make every reasonable effort to remove such personal information from our records, or to flag such personal information and (to the extent permitted by law) retain it for the sole purpose of ensuring that it is no longer used.

### **3.  What is personal information?**

Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, as defined by applicable law. By 'personal information' we mean names, addresses, email addresses, payment information, and any other personal information you voluntarily provide, for example by entering a competition, completing an online questionnaire, or giving credit card details when purchasing products from us. We also collect some personal information automatically when you browse this website, such as your IP address and details of the pages that you have visited.

### **4.  Collecting personal information**

It is your choice to provide us with personal information. In certain instances, we may provide you with the option to select whether you would like to receive information from us or from trusted third parties (for example, by choosing to opt in or opt out of receiving special promotional offers You may choose not to provide any Personal Information to USL, in which case you will not be able to use all the functionalities of the site or receive certain services rendered pursuant to the site.

You may choose to provide us with personal information if, for example, you: contact us with an enquiry; register on the site; forward an item to a friend; purchase an item; fill out a survey or other form with your personal information included; ask us to provide you with information; enter a competition; post information to public areas of the site; or take advantage of a promotion.

By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and clearly consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such information in, other countries or territories. Any such transfer and processing by us will be in accordance with this Privacy and Cookie Notice.

Further, you are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the Personal Information you submit to USL. Inaccurate information may affect your ability to use the site, the information you receive when using the site, and our ability to contact you. For example, your email address should be kept current because that is one of the primary manners in which we communicate with you.

### **5\. IP Addresses**

When your web browser or e-mail application requests a web page or e-mail from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This is called your computer's "IP address." (IP stands for "Internet protocol.") For most users accessing the Internet from a dial-up Internet service provider (ISP), the IP address will be different every time you log on. We receive IP addresses from all users because this information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. We do not store IP addresses in a central database.  They are just recorded in log files so they are not associated with an account.

IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including to:

  * to  identify a person’s country access.
  * To assist our third party service provider to manage GEO IP location, who may map IP addresses to countries.
  * Diagnose service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
  * Send the most appropriate advertising based on geographic area or information derived from your IP address. Many IP addresses are commonly associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major corporations in specific regions or localities. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.
  * Estimate the total number of users visiting our websites from specific countries or regions of the world.
  * Assist third party advertisers to track effectiveness of the promotions they run on our website, visits to and business at third party's websites.
  * Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content that we host.

### **6.  Cookies**

Like many other websites, we use "cookies" to help us gather and store information about visitors to our websites. This notice provides you with information about how we use cookies and how you can control them.  By using this website you accept the use of cookies in accordance with this notice. If you do not accept the use of these cookies, please see the section below entitled ‘How do I disable/enable cookies?’ for further instructions.

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can track unique visitors, recognise returning visitors and remember a visitor’s preferences. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user’s device.

Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving the user experience. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests. You can find more information about cookies at: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### **7\. What types of cookies are used on this site?**

We use two broad categories of cookies:

  * **First party cookies** , served directly by us to your computer.
  * **Third party cookies** , served by a third party on our behalf. We use third party cookies to help us analyse our websites and their uses, and to enable tailored advertising.

### **8.  What do we use cookies for?  **

**Category 1: Strictly Necessary Cookies**

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like shopping baskets or e-billing, cannot be provided.

### **9\. What type of Strictly Necessary Cookies do we use on our website?**

Examples of Strictly Necessary Cookies we may use on this website include Content Management Cookies which are required by the site for the content management system to work and Template Preference Cookies which are necessary for mobile sites and enable the site to look and feel the way it is intended to.

We may also use a Social Sharing Cookie. This is a cookie that identifies you with social networking sites such as Facebook and Twitter and allows interaction between your activity on social networking sites and on our website through your direction, and makes your transition between the sites more seamless.

**Category 2: Performance Cookies**

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.

### **10\. What type of Performance Cookies do we use on on our website?**

We use Google Analytics and Adobe Analytics to help analyse use of the site. This analytical tool uses cookies to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous and aggregate form. The information about your use of the website and your IP address is transmitted to Google and Adobe and is used by us to evaluate visitors' use of the website, compile statistical reports on website activity and create a profile of aggregated visitors using Google Analytics demographics and interests. We also use Google Display Network Impression Reporting to understand which adverts we place on other websites in the Google Display Network are better at helping us attract visitors to our website. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit  <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.   To delete performance cookies, please refer to section 12.

**Category 3: Functionality Cookies**

These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local weather reports or traffic news by storing in a cookie the region in which you are currently located. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

### **11\. What type of Functionality Cookies do we use on our website?**

With your consent we may place a cookie to remember your preferences (Preference Cookie) so that you do not need to re-enter your details (country/age and language preferences) on our gateway page. This is not suitable if you share your computer with someone else.  This cookie expires automatically after 12 months.

We may also use Session Cookies, which are temporary cookies that aid the user journey around the site, and will remember preferences you have selected during the session. These cookies are deleted as soon as you leave the site.

**Category 4: Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies**

These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.

### **12\. What type of Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies do we use on  our website?**

These cookies are used to deliver content that is more relevant to you and your interests based on your previous browsing across the web as well as keywords we may be able to gather from the URLs of webpages from which you accessed this website, your IP address and any search engine used to reach this website. Also these cookies may be used to deliver targeted advertising to you (either within this website or when you visit third party websites) or to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They stay on your computer unless you delete them and they remember that you have visited a website. By choosing ‘accept cookies’ on the cookie notice presented to you when entering this website you are consenting to the use of these types of cookies by us for targeted advertising. For details of how to opt out of these cookies please see the section below entitled “How do I opt out of cookie targeted advertising?”.How do I disable/enable cookies?

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled.

There are a number of ways to manage cookies. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. For example, in Internet Explorer, you can go to the Tools/Internet options/Security and Privacy Tabs to adapt the browser to your expectations. If you use different computers in different locations you will need to ensure that each browser is adjusted to suit your cookie preferences.

Some modern browsers have a feature that will analyse website privacy policies and allow a user to control their privacy needs. These are known as 'P3P' features (Privacy Preferences Platform).

You can easily delete any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser. For example:

How to delete cookies from your Google Chrome browser.

  1. From Google Chrome go to 'Tools Menu'.
  2. Click on 'Options'.
  3. Click on 'Under the Hood'.
  4. Under 'Privacy' section select "Show Cookies'.
  5. A new window should open called 'Cookies'.  In here you can see all the cookies within your Google Chrome Browser.
  6. Click on "Remove All" to remove all traces of cookies.
  7. If you wish to only remove a certain cookie, simply highlight and click "Remove".

How to delete cookies from your Internet Explorer browser.

  1. From Internet Explorer go to ‘Tools Menu’.
  2. Click on ‘Internet Options’.
  3. Click ‘Settings’ under ‘Browser history’ tab.
  4. Click ‘View files’ under ‘Temporary Internet Files’ tab,
  5. Select the files you want to remove and delete them manually.
  6. Note: you can easily identify all cookies by searching for ‘cookie’ against this folder.

If you are not using Microsoft Windows Explorer, then you should select 'cookies' in the 'Help' function for information on where to find your cookie folder.

### **13\. How do I opt out of cookie targeted advertising?**

 If you see any of our advertising with the this logo    on it -  you’re able to take control of whether you get these types of ads.

This is the AdChoices icon and is a part of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s (EDAA).

When you click through the Icon, you’ll get information about the companies that provide interest-based ads on the sites you visit.

You’ll learn about how it works, how this type of advertising supports free content, and about other privacy choices.

If you don’t want this type of advertising, you can click through to the consumer choice page to opt out from the companies that participate in the Icon program.

For further information about how to manage or delete targeted/advertising cookies visit - http://www.youradchoices.com/

### **14.  Use of personal information**

We may use personal information collected from you to provide specific services that you request, as well as to provide additional services that may be of interest.  For example, we may use your personal information in the following ways:

Marketing Communications. We may use your personal information to communicate with you about our products and services, and those of our subsidiaries, affiliates, and parent companies, and any of their related businesses. You have the right to opt-out at any time from receipt of further marketing communications.  You may opt-out by contacting us in accordance with section 10. Unsubscribe, access, questions and further information, below.

Marketing analysis. We may use your personal information for internal marketing analysis, for example, to assess trends amongst our consumers or to measure the amount of traffic to our websites.  We may often aggregate information wherever possible so that it is no longer personal information.

Transactional purposes. We may use your personal information to respond to your queries and requests, maintain your accounts, and manage transactions such as credit card payments for any goods that you order from us or our agents, or for the fulfilment of such transactions (e.g., delivery).

Forward to a friend.  When you provide us with information regarding another individual, such as when you request that we send someone information from one of our websites, we will send that individual only the information you specifically requested that we send. We will not send them additional communications based on your providing us with their information.  You must confirm that your friend is of Legal Purchase Age in the jurisdiction where he/she is located in order for us to transmit the requested information.

### **15.  Disclosure of personal information**

We value your personal information and only share it with third parties that provide it with adequate protection.  From time to time we may disclose personal information  to:

  1. third parties to whom you have provided your consent;
  2. our service providers and subcontractors, including our affiliates, retained to perform functions on our behalf, or to provide services to us (such as warehousing and delivery; marketing and advertising; credit card and data processing; age verification; software development; website hosting and management; information technology and office services; legal, accounting, audit and other professional service providers; and other services related to our business), provided such service providers and subcontractors have entered into written agreements with us and do not collect, use, or disclose the personal information for any purpose other than to perform such functions on our behalf, to provide services to us, or as otherwise required by law;
  3. third parties who, in our reasonable judgment, are providing or seeking the information as your authorized or appointed legal agent; or
  4. We will obtain your express permission before we allow a third party that is not an affiliate to send you any marketing and promotional information;
  5. a person or entity, including our affiliates, in the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, financing, reorganization, or liquidation whereby we transfer, sell, or assign to such third party information concerning your relationship with us, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us;
  6. law enforcement, governmental or regulatory agencies, or other third parties in order to comply with applicable law, or where we believe such action is necessary in order to comply with applicable law, or to detect, protect, or defend us and/or other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, theft, fraud, or other illegal or harmful activity, to comply with our audit and security requirements, or to audit compliance with our corporate policies, procedures, legal, or contractual obligations; and
  7. When you breach this Notice or the Terms of use of the site.

### **16.  Public areas of our websites**

Information that you post on or through the public areas of the site (e.g., chat rooms, bulletin boards, discussion groups, or Social Networking modules) generally is accessible to, and may be collected and used by, others, and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others. You should not provide personal information about yourself in public (or interactive) areas of the site.  Such personal information is not covered under this Privacy and Cookie Notice.

### **17.  Security**

We take security seriously and take precautions to keep your personal information secure. We have implemented security practices and procedures and have a comprehensively documented information security programme and information security policies with adequate managerial, technical, operational and physical security control measures to safeguard against any non-disclosure of your personal information that we collect. However, we have no control over the privacy of any communication while it is in transit to us. We therefore recommend that you not include confidential, proprietary, or sensitive information in any such communications.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us at the contact details below.In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If such a notification is appropriate, we will endeavour to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email.

You are reminded that, in accordance with the Terms of Use for this website, which include this Privacy and Cookie Notice, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you are responsible for any activity under your account and password.  It is your sole responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify us when you wish to cancel your account.  We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this obligation.

While USL will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information and other information submitted by you is safe and secure, it offers no representation, warranties or other assurances that the security measures are adequate, safe, fool proof or impenetrable.

### **18.  Unsubscribe, access, questions and further information**

At your request and where the law requires us to do so, you may contact us (using the unsubscribe details provided below) and  we will confirm what personal information we hold about you, update your information, remove your information, fulfil specific opt-out requests (including requests where you previously opted in with respect to the use of your personal information), and/or correct any inaccuracies in such personal information.  You may also have the right to obtain a copy of all personal information we hold about you. Where you choose to provide specific opt-out requests (including requests where you previously opted in with respect to the use of your personal information), you will not be able to use all the functionalities of the site or receive certain services rendered pursuant to the site.

### **19\. Retention period**

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.  

If you would like to unsubscribe from this communication, or from all communications about Diageo brands, please contact: admin@liveinstyle.com

### **20.  Portfolio permissions**

If you have given permission to receive communications about Diageo brands generally (for example, by opting to receive news and special offers by email about Diageo’s other great alcohol brands), you may from time to time receive communications about brands to which you have not opted in specifically. Information about many of Diageo’s brands can be found at [www.diageobrands.com](http://www.diageobrands.com/).

We occasionally may send you communications about brands not featured on [www.diageobrands.com](http://www.diageobrands.com/) (e.g., new brands). We recommend that you refer to [www.diageobrands.com](http://www.diageobrands.com/) from time to time as the list of featured brands will be updated periodically.

Providing general permission for us to communicate with you about our brands does not mean that you will receive communications about all of Diageo’s brands. We will only communicate with you about those brands that we think may be of particular interest to you. Any such communications will provide you with an opportunity to unsubscribe from the brand in question and/or from all communications about Diageo brands.

If you have any privacy-related questions, concerns or complaints, please contact: admin@liveinstyle.com

### **21.  Interfaces with Third-Party Websites**

The site may contain links, references, and content from other websites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have limited or no control over these websites and our Privacy and Cookie Notice does not apply to these sites. We encourage you to read the Privacy and Cookie Notices and Conditions of Use of any linked, referenced, or interfacing websites you enter.

This Privacy and Cookie Notice will be supplemented by additional legal requirements in jurisdictions where we conduct business as required. Nothing in this Privacy and Cookie Notice or otherwise will create, or add to, any right or claim (whether legal, equitable, or otherwise) that any individual or person may have at law or otherwise against the company or any third party, or any of their respective directors, officers, employees, agents, or representatives (collectively the “Diageo Group”), nor will the existence of this Privacy and Cookie Notice or its application impose or add to any obligations upon or create any liability for the Diageo Group that it does not already otherwise have under law.

© [2016]) All rights reserved.  Version 9.6 dated 2016.
